The Look of Silence is a history, documentary film
directed by Joshua Oppenheimer.
An optician grapples with the Indonesian mass killings of
1965-1966, during which his older brother was exterminated.
Self, played by Adi Rukun.
Self, played by M.Y. Basrun.
Self (archive footage), played by Amir Hasan.
Self, played by Inong.
Self, played by Kemat.
Self (voice), played by Joshua Oppenheimer.
The Look of Silence (Indonesian: Senyap, "Silence") is a 2014 internationally co-produced documentary
film directed by Joshua Oppenheimer about the Indonesian mass killings of 1965–66.
The film is a companion piece to his 2012 documentary The Act of Killing.
Executive producers were Werner Herzog, Errol Morris, and Andre Singer.
It was nominated for the Academy Award for Best
Documentary Feature at the 88th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of loss of loved one, mass
murder, biography, indonesia, torture.